royalcm.com 2016-03-22

# Royal CM - Home

This privacy policy applies to http://www.royalcm.com ("RoyalCM"), owned and operated by Riverjor dba NationTraffic. This privacy policy describes how RoyalCM collects and uses the personal information clients provide on this web site: http://www.royalcm.com. It also describes the available choices regarding the use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

1\. When clients register with RoyalCM they acknowledge their willingness to share with the company certain private information (name, email, gender, age, address and billing information such as credit card number, bank account information) which we use for the purpose of confirming the client's identity and ensuring the security of their deposits and trading account. This information is collected in line with our stringent verification procedures which are used to deter international money laundering operations and to ensure the security and safety of our customer's trading activity throughout. 

2\. Our clients undertake to supply us with true, updated and accurate information about their identity. Furthermore they are required to state categorically that they are registering and trading on their own behalf and are not seeking at any time to act any manner which could be considered fraudulent nor are they seeking to impersonate any other individuals for any purposes whatsoever. 

3\. RoyalCM's data collection procedures include the collection of client's freely disclosed information as shared with the company, in addition to the placement of cookies for the purposes of gathering data about the manner in which client's interact with the RoyalCM website. These tools for gathering client's information are employed for the purpose of ensuring the customer's own security and all data collected by the company is shared only with individuals within the company who are involved with the verification of customer account information for the express purpose of ensuring the customer's confidentiality and security. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time (30 days). You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as: cashier, my account section, contests or surveys, will be limited. 

The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the cashier. 

4\. RoyalCM will never disclose any private or otherwise confidential information in regards to our clients and former clients to third parties without the express, written consent of our clients, except in such specific cases in which disclosure is a requirement under law, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request or is otherwise necessary in order to perform verification analysis on the client's identity for the purposes of safeguarding their account and securing their personal information. If Riverjor S.A. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

5\. By registering with RoyalCM and through the voluntary interaction they undertake with RoyalCM's products and services the client confirms and agrees that they consent to the use of all or part of the information they supply concerning their RoyalCM trading account, the transactions they undertake through it and the interactions which they perform with the company on behalf of the company. All interactions the customer undertakes with the cmpanywill be stored by the company for the purposes of record and as such may be employed by the company in such cases that disputes arise between clients and RoyalCM. 

6\. RoyalCM does its utmost to ensure the confidentiality of its clients personal information including the implementation of data protection procedures designed to ensure client confidentiality. RoyalCM ensures that its data protection policy is regularly updated in order to ensure that client's confidential information is continually safeguarded. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

7\. From time to time RoyalCM may contact clients whether by phone or email for the purpose of offering them further information about RoyalCM, binary options trading or financial market trading. In addition the company may, on occasion, seek to contact clients, whether by phone or by email, for the purpose of informing them of unique promotional offerings provided by RoyalCM for the client. Clients consent to the receipt of such contact when they consent to our terms and conditions of use when registering with RoyalCM . Any person wishing to opt out of further contact with RoyalCM at anytime whatsoever is entitled to do so, simply by contacting the company whether by phone or email as listed below and requesting that no further contact on behalf of the company be made.
